<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>QuestInLanka</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on QuestInLanka</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://questinlanka.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 13:49:50 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://questinlanka.github.io/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/terms/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 13:49:50 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://questinlanka.github.io/terms/</guid><description>INTRODUCTION Welcome to Questinlanka, a website operated by QuestInLanka (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). These Terms and Conditions govern your use of our website, services, and products. By accessing or using our website, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these Terms and Conditions, please do not use our website.
USE OF OUT WEBSITE Our website is intended for personal and non-commercial use only.</description></item><item><title>Thanks for Contacting Us</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/contact_thanks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 13:38:38 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://questinlanka.github.io/contact_thanks/</guid><description>Thanks for touching base with us. Someone from Alpha Church will be in touch soon.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://questinlanka.github.io/about/</guid><description>Welcome to Questinlanka – a travel agency based in Sri Lanka that is dedicated to providing the best possible travel experiences to visitors from around the world. At Questinlanka, we believe that traveling is not just about sightseeing, but also about experiencing the local culture and lifestyle. Our team of travel experts is passionate about showcasing the beauty and diversity of Sri Lanka, and we strive to make every trip with us an unforgettable experience.</description></item><item><title>9-Days Tour Package</title><link>https://questinlanka.github.io/tours/9days/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://questinlanka.github.io/tours/9days/</guid><description>Day 1-2: Sigiriya and Dambulla Travel to the ancient city of Sigiriya, home to the famous Sigiriya Rock Fortress, which is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Also, explore the stunning Dambulla Cave Temples and the vibrant local markets.
Day 3: Kandy Travel to the cultural city of Kandy, home to the famous Temple of the Tooth Relic, which is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Also, explore the stunning Royal Botanic Gardens, the scenic Kandy Lake, and the vibrant local markets.</description></item></channel></rss>